Why-- you have to--
你為什么要...
why are you doing it like that?
你為什么要那么做
You have to fold, fold, okay?
你得把它們疊好
We have very little time, left. Please.
我們的時間可不多  拜托
Holy shit, you guys!
我去  各位啊
He's cooking something, it's water,
他在煮東西  是水
but congratulations.
但恭喜了
There's heat involved.
至少還在加熱
It's cooking!
是烹飪
Fuck!
該死
Who won the polenta challenge?
誰贏了玉米粥挑戰
We shoot that later, okay?
我們待會兒再拍那個
But if it is up to me,
但如果要我說了算
none of those people, because they're just--
他們都贏不了  因為他們...
they're all so awful at cooking in general.
他們全都太不會烹飪了
Please, please don't fall off my bar.
請別從我的吧臺上掉下來
Okay, look, I'm just spitballing here.
好吧  我就隨便說說
Mm-hm, sock it to me.
嗯  說吧
I want it.
我想聽
You be my plus one.
你做我的伴
You want me to crash your mom's wedding?
你要我去參加你媽的婚禮
Come here, come here.
過來
But it's gonna be so weird.
但那會很奇怪的
Sit down.
坐下
Mouse, I wasn't invited, okay?
小老鼠  我沒受邀  好嗎
Ex-spouses don't usually make the cut.
前任一般不會被請去
Copy that.
收到
Hey, five minutes, Mr. Rake.
五分鐘  雷克先生
Okay.
好
Riley, uh...
萊利
your mom loves you very much.
你媽媽非常愛你
And I love you very, very much,
我也非常愛你
not that it's a competition.
雖然這不是競爭
But listen to me.
但聽我說
Nothing's gonna change
這周末之后
after this weekend.
也不會有什么改變
Okay?
好嗎
Except your mom's new last name will be "Geck."
但你媽媽的新姓氏將變成"蓋可"
That's unfortunate.
這太不幸了
So, I think we should just give them this day
我覺得我們該讓他們好好度過這一天
and then next weekend,
然后下周末
you and me?
我們倆
We take on the world.
我們去應付全世界
Okay?
好嗎
Well, how about we start tonight?
我們今晚就開始吧
Darnell Park just cut the ribbon on a new mini golf course.
達奈爾公園剛建成了新迷你高爾夫球場
And why do you think I gave Katie instructions
所以我才叫凱蒂
to have you there by 6 PM
晚6點前送你過去
so that you can see the sun setting
這樣你就可以站在
behind the freshly painted, sized-to-scale windmill?
新粉刷的1:1風車后面欣賞落日了
Hey buddy.
好啊  伙計
Come on, not this weekend, man.
拜托  這周末不行啊
Okay. Hey, one sec.
好吧  等一下的
Oh! Okay.
好吧
Look, do I want to be the one that golfs with you?
我想陪你一起去打高爾夫嗎
Of course. I just have so much work to do
當然了  但我這周末有太多
this weekend, and you deserve better
工作要做了  你應該得到
than my distracted company, okay?
比我更專心的陪伴  好嗎
Yeah, well, your company's often distracted.
你陪我的時候往往是心不在焉
I handed that one to you, okay?
這個我承認
I gave that to you for free.
免費承認
Had a bow on it.
系個蝴蝶結吧
Next Saturday,
下周六
you, me, Darnell Park.
你  我  達奈爾公園
Okay, but I have a soccer game next Saturday.
但我下周六要踢足球
It was a test.
那是測試
Congratulations, you've passed.
恭喜  你通過了
What I meant to say is next Sunday
我是想說  下周日
will be off the chain.
我們肯定玩瘋
Never say "off the chain."
別說"玩瘋"
- Whatever's clever. - Don't.
-反正是句俏皮話  -別傻了
I don't know what plays anymore.
我都不知道現在流行語是什么了
Babe, what plays?
親愛的  什么流行
Tell me.
告訴我
Okay, well, "rad"'s back.
"酷"又回來了
Oh! Katie, "rad"'s back.
凱蒂  "酷"又回來了
- Did you know that? - "rad"'s back!
-你知道嗎  -"酷"又回來了
Yeah. You are so rad.
是啊  你好酷啊
Yeah, well, your floppy hair is rad.
你的亂發又很酷
Hey, um, please drive carefully
開車要小心
because this is my most precious cargo,
這可是我最貴重的貨物
and, uh, call me if anything goes sideways,
如果有什么情況打給我
and would you please feed yourselves?
給自己弄點吃的
Thanks. Have a great weekend.
謝謝  周末愉快
- We got this. - Of course.
-我們可以的  -當然
Yup.
嗯
You are my only.
你是我的唯一
I need you.
我需要你
Bye!
再見
Okay.
好吧
Barry, I have done what you've asked,
巴里  我已經照你的要求做了
and I am skipping town for the weekend, okay?
我周末要離鎮
Now please tell me what you're doing,
拜托告訴我你要做什么
and, spoiler alert, it better have some fuckin' teeth.
劇透  最好是有牙的家伙
You got a light?
你有火嗎
Yeah.
嗯
Keep it.
給你了
Trying to quit.
我想戒呢
We're all trying to quit.
我們都想戒
I'll treat her like she was my own.
我會對它視如己出
- Ooh, sorry. - It's okay.
-抱歉  -沒事
Thank you.
謝謝
All right.
好吧
Ready, let's go.
好了  我們走吧
Okay, let's go.
好了  走吧
It's not enough.
這不夠
- No, it's good. - What?
-行的  -什么
Wait, what kind of beer is that?
這是什么啤酒
Hold this, someone.
誰拿一下
I am with you, but also you don't want them
我理解你  但你不希望她們覺得
to think you make suits out of lady skins, right?
你是拿女人皮做衣服的變態吧
Yes, let's go.
我們走吧
No way.
不會吧
Peter Rake.
彼得·雷克
Yeah, yes, I am, I am Chef Peter in the flesh.
是啊  我是彼得大廚本人
Oh, holy shit.
我去
Holy shit, you used to work here in high school, didn't you?
你高中時就在這里工作  是吧
Lenny.
萊尼
Lonnie.
朗尼
This is, um...
這里
It's all mine now.
現在是我的了
Booya, man, this is...
厲害  哥們
this is really great for you.
這真不錯呢
Yeah, my dad kicked the bucket a few years back.
嗯  我爸幾年前死了
The cancer ate him up.
被癌癥吞噬了
Shit, I'm sorry to hear that, man.
我去  我很遺憾
It's okay.
沒事的
He was a mean son of a bitch.
他是個混蛋
Well, you know, the same thing happened to my old man,
我老爸也是這樣
and he wasn't much of a prize either.
他也不怎么樣
Yeah.
嗯
So now it's just me and Mother.
現在只有我和我母親了
"Mother," Huh?
"母親"啊
You guys think about diversifying a little bit?
你們考慮過多元化一下嗎
Maybe you could add a few rooms,
或許加幾個房間
poke some tiny holes in the wall,
在墻上開個洞
call it Bait Motel, huh?
改名叫貝茨旅館
Lonnie, what's--what's down here?
朗尼  這里是什么
Is this where you keep the baskets and the washing, huh?
你放籃子和換洗衣物的地方嗎
Sorry, that was stupid. It's--
抱歉  我太傻了
The place looks great, it really does.
這地方看上去很棒  真的
You know, you have bins,
你有垃圾桶
stills just filled with bait.
全是魚餌的掛畫
It's exactly the same.
真是一點沒變
It's--it's great.
太棒了
Yeah, sister used to come around
你妹妹以前常來
pretty regular for a while.
有一陣很頻繁
Oh, my sister, that's right.
我妹妹  對啊
Tell you what, I'll take a pack of Kools
這樣吧  我要一包庫茲煙
and--and keep the change.
不用找了
- It's on me. - No, that's ridiculous.
-我請你了  -不  那怎么行
Your money's no good here.
你的錢在這里沒用
These...
這...
These are perfect, and that's-- that's sweet.
很棒  你太貼心了
Thank you, sir.
謝謝
I'm gonna tell Gwen that, uh--
我會告訴格溫...
Wait, um...
等等
Is she here?
她來了嗎
No, no, she's not.
沒有
She--she hardly ever makes it down here.
她現在幾乎不怎么來這邊了
She never-- she never makes it back.
她都不回來了
But I'm gonna tell her that--
但我會告訴她...
Lonnie says...
朗尼會說
*Hey Gwennie*
*嗨  格溫*
Yeah, she's gonna love that.
她肯定會喜歡的
Thanks, man.
謝謝了
Hey Zan.
詹
Hey Jayna.
潔雅
Oh, we are so Wonder Twinning right there.
我們那時真是神奇雙胞胎
Speaking of our youth, uh...
說到青春時期
Agnes was what, 60 years old when we were kids,
艾格尼絲在我們小時候就60多了吧
which would put her at, right now,
那她現在就...
at least a solid hunge, right?
至少一百了吧
- A hunge and a deuce? - Yeah.
-超過一百了  -嗯
And she would still whoop your ass.
那她也還能收拾你
He'll be upstairs,
他去樓上住
your father's old office.
你父親的舊辦公室
It's a bedroom now.
現在是臥室了
Thank God.
謝天謝地
I would rather sleep outside
我寧可睡外面
than in our dead parents' stone cold bed.
也不想睡我們死去父母冰冷的床
Hey, Agnes, please, please, please.
艾格尼絲  別這樣
You don't have to carry my--my bag up the stairs.
你不用替我把包拿到樓上
Can I just--can I get you a weekend at a Nordic spa
我安排你去北歐水療
or something?
玩一周末吧
No.
不用了
Okay.
好吧
So how's my one and only niece?
我唯一的侄女怎么樣了
Here you go.
看看吧
Oh my God.
天吶
- Are you kidding me? - I'm not kidding you.
-開玩笑嗎  -沒有
She is 11 going on Michelle Obama.
她11歲了  越來越像米歇爾·奧巴馬
Oh, I follow her on Instagram,
我在圖片分享上粉了她
but she doesn't really do selfies.
但她不怎么拍自拍
I've racked my brains, I can't figure out
我怎么也想不通
where she gets the humility from.
她這謙虛的勁頭跟誰學的
Gwen, I don't know.
格溫  我不知道
- Not me. - No, not you.
-不是跟我學的  -是啊
So that's it?
沒了嗎
Really?
真的
Just a couple recipes
就幾份食譜
and a few breaths of fresh air?
和呼吸新鮮空氣
That's all that's going on here?
你就是為了這個而來嗎
I mean, you have no idea how fucked up it's been
你不知道一直見不到你
not seeing you and not hearing from you.
沒有你的消息  我都難受
I'd argue I know exactly how fucked up it's been.
我非常清楚這多難受
My number hasn't changed.
我的號碼沒變過
You know?
知道嗎
I'm the one who went through a divorce, right?
我才是離了婚的那個
I'm the one that wasn't welcome at Dad's funeral.
我才是不能參加爸爸葬禮的那個
Yeah, okay, point taken.
好  我知道了
Okay.
好
You remember what you said to me
你記得你上次對我
the last time?
說了什么嗎
I was going through some shit, Gwen, okay?
我當時很艱難  格溫  好嗎
And then Dad cuts me out,
然后爸爸剝奪了我的繼承權
but I needed you to fuckin' have--
但我需要你
Have your back no matter what.
無論如何都支持你
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah, how have you been?
你還好嗎
You're just still fightin' the good fight?
你還在為正義而戰嗎
Datin' anybody?
有跟誰約會嗎
With all the free time I have?
因為我那么有閑嗎
Ah, shit.
該死
Guess who else is single?
猜猜還有誰是單身
- Colin Farrell? - Not even close.
-柯林·法瑞爾  -差遠了
Lonnie from high school.
高中的朗尼
Bunny boiler Lonnie.
煮兔子的朗尼
Yeah.
嗯
He's running the bait shop
他現在在自己開一家
all by himself now.
魚餌店
I know.
是啊
I have not thought about him in a very long time.
我已經很久沒想過他了
Well, I mean, Christ, I would be worried if you had.
天吶  如果你想他了我才擔心呢
But he does-- he does say...
但他說
*Hey Gwennie*
*嗨  格溫*
So you've got that going for you.
你還有這個選擇呢
- Okay? - You spoke to him?
-好嗎  -你跟他說話了
I did, and he still has that sweet butt chin.
是啊  他還有那個可愛的屁股下巴
- Okay, stop that. - It's nice, okay.
-好了  夠了  -挺好的
He was just trying to be my friend, you know that.
他只是想做我的朋友  你知道的
But you played the tuba in marching band.
但你是軍樂隊的大號手
Gwen, hanging out with Lonnie
格溫  如果你還跟朗尼玩
would have been the final death nail
你在高中就算
in your high school shit coffin.
別想翻身了
You're welcome.
不客氣
So why now?
為什么現在見面
You know, I miss you.
我想你了
You're the other half of my very special brain.
你是我特別大腦的另一半
Come on.
得了
I'm right here.
我在這兒呢
Just talk to me.
跟我說吧
It's the fuckin' internet.
是該死的互聯網
You can't...
你不能...
I'm an easy target.
我太容易針對了
Gwen, you know this, you know this.
格溫  你清楚的
We vet these people the best way we can,
我們已經盡可能地審查這些人了
but, oh, God, heads are gonna roll.
但天吶  肯定要有人遭殃的
Mark my words, you mess with the bull...
相信我  敢惹公牛
You get the horns.
就被捅
- Got it. - No, you don't got it.
-知道了  -不  你不懂
That's why we haven't spoken for three years, Gwen.
所以我們才三年沒說話了
Shit.
該死
I gotta take this.
我得接一下
Oh, okay.
好吧
Andy, what have you got?
安迪  什么情況
You hungry?
你餓了嗎
Are we farmers, Agnes?
我們成農民了嗎  艾格尼絲
What are you going on about?
你說什么呢
I'm talking about Black Phillip
那只魔鬼般的黑羊
prancing about the...
就在...
Okay, well...
好吧
never mind, but...
當我沒說
Good to see you, boy.
見到你很高興  孩子
Agnes.
艾格尼絲
God, you are such a bad liar.
天吶  你真不會說謊
You're gonna hate me.
你會恨我的
"Hate" is a strong and sticky word.
"恨"是個強烈  不好擺脫的詞
I have to leave.
我得走了
Yeah. The, um, lead detective in my double homicide
嗯  我雙尸案的負責警探
just picked up the second shooter.
剛抓了第二位槍手
They're saying he's willing to talk,
他們說他愿意開口
but only to the DA,
但只肯對地檢官說
which happens to be me.
而那是我
You?
你嗎
That's incredible.
難以置信
That's fucking-- that's incredible.
那太難以置信了
When, when?
什么時候
- Five months. - Oh my...
-五個月了  -天吶
Yeah, I wanted to call you, but--
我想打給你的
Shit, my sister is the DA.
我妹妹是地檢官了
You're not fucking kidding me?
你沒開玩笑吧
We have to celebrate.
我們得慶祝一下
- Let's celebrate. - No, we will.
-我們慶祝吧  -我們會的
We will, I promise, I promise.
真的  我保證
Yeah, I wanted to spend the whole weekend with you.
我想陪你一周末的
Okay, well, there's-- you know,
沒事
there's endless weekends.
還有好多周末呢
- Really? - If I have my way, yes.
-是嗎  -如果我說了算的話
Okay.
好
Well, I will call with updates.
我有新情況會告訴你
Please do.
那好
- Okay, bye. - Oh, yeah.
-再見  -嗯
- Thanks. - All right.
-謝謝  -好
Hey, Ags, whatever happened
艾格尼絲  這墻上之前掛的
to the gentle, Bob Ross-esque Alaskan landscape
鮑勃·羅斯先生畫的溫婉的
that used to adorn this wall?
阿拉斯加景色呢
Your father moved it
你父親取下來了
when he took up painting.
因為他開始畫畫了
It's pretty much all he did towards the end.
他最后就干這個
That one's his.
那是他畫的
Nice.
好啊
But also, what the actual fuck?
但這什么玩意啊
His pieces were all about
他畫的都是
the fragility of life.
生命的脆弱
How was his funeral?
他的葬禮如何
Cold.
冰冷
That's fitting.
合適
Uh, hey, Ags?
艾格尼絲
I don't mean any offense, but have you ever thought about
無意冒犯  但你考慮過
having a doctor take a look
找醫生看看
at those... sweet peepers?
你的眼睛嗎
What for?
何必
It's the things I can't unsee
是我忘不了的事情
that keep me up at night.
讓我夜不能寐
Ags, could you get the phone, please?
艾格尼絲  可以接下電話嗎
Shit!
該死
Oh, fuck you, man.
去你的
- Hello? - Hi Peter.
-喂  -彼得
It's Lonnie.
我是朗尼
From Bait and Tackle.
魚餌和魚線的
I know who you are, Lonnie.
我知道你是誰  朗尼
Um, didn't know this number was listed, though.
但我不知道黃頁上有我們的電話
Was that-- was that you that was calling earlier?
之前也是你打來的嗎
- Buddy? - Earlier?
-哥們  -之前
Mm, no that wasn't me.
沒有  不是我
You--you sure you weren't calling me before, Lonnie?
你確定你之前沒打給我嗎  朗尼
I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
我只是想確認你還好
Yeah, no, I'm okay.
我挺好
Thank you, man, I'm just--
謝謝  哥們
it's quick in, out, you know?
我就小住一下
Pickin' up a few things, so...
就拿幾樣東西
Lonnie, you still there?
朗尼  你還在嗎
You did really good, Peter.
你混得真不錯  彼得
On TV and everything.
還上了電視什么的
I'm just really happy for you.
我很為你高興
Okay.
好吧
Shit.
該死
Yo, Pete, it's Barry.
彼得  我是巴里
Uh... look dude, after doing some more recon,
聽我說  我調查過后
I'm confident we'll be able to settle this, okay?
相信我們能解決這個問題
It's basically rinse and repeat.
基本上就是重復取證
There's no reason to drag this one through the mud
這次沒必要搞得太難看
unless you're willing to go on record,
除非你想被記錄在案
which I certainly wouldn't advise.
我當然不建議你這么做
Uh, you can holler back
你可以給我回電話
if you want me to bill you my weekend rate. Uh...
如果你想按照我的周末收費標準給錢的話
Look, dude, just try to relax.
兄弟  放松一下
Don't go down any rabbit holes on the web, all right?
別去網上探索未知世界  好嗎
Ciao.
再見
Hi, can I help you?
你好  有什么事嗎
Hi.
你好
Didn't I see you back at the Bait and Tackle?
我是不是在魚餌和魚線見過你
Yes, yes, and I saw you.
是的  我看見你了
There--there was a-- there was a moment.
有那么一瞬間
It was brief, but we shared it.
雖然很短暫  但我們四目相對了
Hi, I'm Peter.
你好  我是彼得
Kara.
卡拉
I'm-- I'm really sorry to bother you.
很抱歉打擾你
We're just--we're in a pickle.
只是我們遇到了麻煩
Cross the canyon lost power,
穿過峽谷之后車壞了
back-up Jenny pooped out.
備用修理員珍妮筋疲力盡
It's putting a-- a big damper
這就像是給單身女子的周末
on bachelorette weekend.
裝了個巨大的阻尼器
- So it's-- - You need flashlights,
-這真是...  -所以你需要手電筒
candles, and SPAM.
蠟燭和午餐肉
- You read my mind. - Okay, come on in.
-你讀懂了我的心  -好吧  進來吧
Let's uh, see what we've got.
我們看看都有什么
Or you stay right there
或者你就站在這兒
and I will bring the items to you.
我把東西拿給你
You don't know if I'm Ted Bundy, do you?
你不知道我是不是泰德·邦迪[連環殺手]  對吧
Uh, but I have to warn you,
但我必須要警告你
it might take me, like, a minute
可能我需要花一分鐘的時間
to find the items we're discussing
去找我們剛剛說的物品
because I have not been home
因為我自從銹根樂隊解散之后
since Rusted Root was the shit.
就沒來過這里
You know what, Peter, it's-- it's cold.
你知道嗎  彼得  很冷
I'm cold, and that's on me.
我很冷  都怪我自己
So lead the way.
所以  帶路吧
Okay.
好的
Uh, we can leave this door open.
我們可以把門開著
You know, you do have his cheekbones.
你確實有他的顴骨
Whose cheekbones?
誰的顴骨
Ted Bundy.
泰德·邦迪[連環殺手]
You are sharp.
你眼神真好
It only takes a spark
只需要一點火花
but we need more.
但我們需要更多
That's not a closet.
這不是壁櫥
It's not.
確實不是
Good to know.
很高興知道
It's good to know.
很高興知道這不是
I'm flying blind here.
我迷路了
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
That's all right.
沒事的
This place is--
這個地方真是...
Awful, tacky?
又臟又俗嗎
Everything that's wrong with old money?
這點錢全都花錯地方了
There's just no accounting for taste.
品味是買不來的
You know what?
你知道嗎
I was gonna say "Beautiful."
我本來想說"漂亮"的
I mean, the views are incredible.
這里的景色太美了
Okay.
好吧
So, uh, you are a musician, huh?
所以你是一位音樂家  對吧
I read minds.
我會讀心啊
Plus, I noticed the calluses on your fingertips,
而且我注意到了你指尖上的老繭
which is a sure sign
這是這位女士彈吉他
the young lady plays the six strings.
確切的跡象
Yeah, I make the big bucks
沒錯  我在咖啡店和二手書店
playing coffee shops and used book stores, so...
彈琴賺了不少錢
eat a lot of ramen.
吃了許多拉面
I can appreciate that.
我很欣賞這點
Just like you can appreciate these.
就像你會很感謝這些一樣
- Peter? - Yes?
-彼得  -怎么了
I know a handful of ladies
很多女士肯定會
who are gonna think you're a real prince.
認為你是真正的王子
Ribbit.
那挺好
Uh, you have my number if things deteriorate in a meaningful way.
如果事情變得更糟了  你有我的電話
I do, neighbor.
我會的  鄰居
Or, you know,
或者
maybe I'll just run out of milk.
或許我只是牛奶喝完了
Good morning, you old bastard.
早上好  你這個老東西
No rest for the weary, huh?
討厭的人得不到休息  是吧
I'm in my prime, asshole.
我正處于盛年  混蛋
Please, please. No, no.
拜托  拜托  不要
Wait.
等等
Peter!
彼得
- Hey. - Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
-你好  -糟糕  抱歉
I didn't-- I didn't see the ear buds.
我沒看見你戴著耳機
- Everything makes sense now. - Yeah.
-現在一切都說得通了  -是啊
No, I'm totally not deaf.
我當然沒聾
Uh, welcome to The Shire.
歡迎來到夏爾郡
Oh, yeah.
是啊
- Cool tree house. - Thank you.
-樹屋挺酷  -謝謝你
Thank you very much.
非常感謝你
Man, can't believe that thing is still standing.
老天  真不敢相信它還沒塌
Me and my sister used to basically move in there every summer.
以前我和我姐姐一到夏天就搬進去
Now, some jerk has put a weird thing on the thing,
現在有些混蛋在上面放了些奇怪的東西
but, hey, how did you guys make out?
你們最后怎么樣了
How did you fare?
你們的進展怎么樣
Oh, not great.
不是很好
The electrician can't get out till Monday.
電工要到星期一才能上班
- But... - Shit.
-但是...  -糟糕
Lemonade out of lemons.
世事無常  要勇敢面對
Last night ended up being really fun.
昨天晚上還是很愉快的
- Oh, nice. - Yeah.
-挺好的  -是的
- Hi tortoises. - It's not a God damn race.
-你好  烏龜  -這不是比賽
While you were jogging getting swamp ass,
當你慢跑  把渾身弄得黏糊糊的時候
we were sharing our hopes and dreams.
我們在分享我們的希望和夢想
That's right, we keep it on the 100.
沒錯  我們始終保持滿分
Marie, Elena,
瑪麗  艾琳娜
like a good neighbor, Peter was there.
我們的好鄰居彼得昨天幫了大忙
Yeah, that was dope, man.
那真是太棒了  老兄
Thank you.
謝謝你
Thank you very much. It's the least I could do.
謝謝你們  這是最起碼的
Uh, and if I were to take a shot in the dark,
如果我要盲猜一下
would presume that you are the soon-to-be kept woman.
我猜你馬上要成為家庭主婦了
Have you ever Googled "Kept woman"?
你上網查過"家庭主婦"這個詞嗎
You familiar with the Urban Dictionary?
你熟悉俚語詞典嗎
Oh shit.
糟了
I'm sorry, I thought that was a--
對不起  我以為這是...
that was an okay phrase.
這是一個好詞
Um, I--I did not mean to offend you and--
我沒有要冒犯你的意思
I'm just playing with you.
我跟你開玩笑呢
- Solid. - Saw his face?
-好吧  -看見他的臉了嗎
The blood just drained.
都面無血色了
That was nice.
真是個不錯的玩笑
Oh my God, I recognize you.
我的天  我認識你
No, I'm not Amy Adams.
不  我不是艾米·亞當斯[演員]
- People do-- - No, no, no.
-人們確實...  -不不不
You're that chef.
你是那個主廚
I seen you on TV.
我在電視上見過你
You have that show that's, like,
你有一個節目
a facsimile of another show with a more famous chef?
是另一個更有名的廚師的節目的復制版
Thank you if you meant that sweetly in any way.
如果你是好意的話  那就謝謝你了
And I don't think you did.
雖然我不這么覺得
But still, thank you for recognizing me.
但還是要謝謝你認出我來
Um, so what are you guys gonna do?
所以你們打算干什么
We're gonna stay.
我們打算留下
It's like glamping.
就像豪華露營
Oh, okay, so you're gonna make some lemonade?
所以你打算勇敢面對了嗎
Okay, well, we thrown in the towel.
好吧  我們認輸了
Translation, if we don't get back,
她的意思是說  如果我們不回去的話
Mom and Morgan will smoke all of our weed.
媽媽和茉根會把我們所有的大麻都吸完
Thanks for the fire, Chef Boyardee.
感謝你的蠟燭  男廚神
Check you later.
回頭見
Come on up and take it easy.
來吧  別緊張
Pray for Puerto Rico.
為波多黎各禱告
- Okay. - See you in a few.
-好吧  -一會兒見
Aw, Chef Boyardee.
男廚神
- That's funny. - So you, uh, you run?
-還挺有趣的  -所以你跑步嗎
When chased, yes.
追人的時候會跑的
And quickly.
而且跑得很快
I think you're being modest.
我覺得你在謙虛
That headband didn't cut itself off your favorite old tee.
這個頭巾是不是從你以前最喜歡的襯衫上剪的
- This old thing? - Mm-hm.
-這個老東西嗎  -是啊
Hey, I have a-- I have a crazy idea.
我有個瘋狂的想法
You want to freeze the lake so we can curl all weekend?
你想讓湖結冰  周末我們能在上面打滾嗎
I really do want to do that.
我確實想這么做
That's a-- but first, I want to cook for you
但首先  我想給你
and your friends.
和你的朋友做頓飯
Uh, and before you say anything,
在你開口之前
uh, I just want to let you know
我想讓你知道
you'd be doing me a huge solid
你會幫我一個大忙的
'cause I have, I don't know, three or four recipes I need to work out
因為在我最暢銷的食譜書中
for my new most likely bestselling cookbook.
有三  四個食譜我需要試驗一下
Humble brag.
不是吹牛
And you want us as your guinea pigs
你想讓我們在你的大房子里
- in your big fancy house? - Well.
-當你的小白鼠  -是的
What time would this theoretical multi-course feast kick off?
這場理論的盛宴何時開始
Um, well, I--I do find that
我確實發現
sunset pairs just perfectly with an amuse-bouche.
日落配上開胃小菜堪稱完美
Any "Bouche", really.
什么"小菜"都行  真的
*Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags, Ags*
*艾格尼絲啊艾格尼絲*
*Ags got one potato*
*艾格尼絲拿著一個土豆*
Gotta take our shoes off.
我們得把鞋脫了
I don't want to take our shoes off.
我不想把鞋脫了
You know what I mean?
你知道我什么意思嗎
Maybe it's one of those houses
或許這個房子
where you have to take your shoes off.
也是那種你需要脫鞋的房子
- Hi. - Welcome, ladies.
-你好啊  -歡迎  女士們
I think you'll find ample electric light.
我想你們會找到充足的電燈
Oh, look at all this white privilege.
看看這些白人特權
Help yourself.
你們自便
This is my mom, Lilith.
這是我的媽媽  莉莉絲
Hello, you, again.
你好啊
- Well, you lit up my life. - Thank you.
-畢竟你讓我的生活充滿光彩  -謝謝你
- You helped me quit smoking. - Oh, well.
-你幫我戒了煙  -好吧
You know the family resemblance is striking, you two.
你們兩個長得真像
Oh, I know.
我知道
Well, one night with Desmond Tutu changed my life forever.
南非大主教
That's fun, you're fun.
真好笑  你真幽默
- We are fun. - You are.
-我們都很幽默  -是的
- This painting. - Oh, I know.
-這幅畫  -我知道
I'm sorry-- Agnes?
我很抱歉  艾格尼絲
You know, I asked her to take that down because it is so morbid.
我讓她拿下來  因為這太恐怖了
- Oh, I like it. - Me too.
-我喜歡  -我也是
I like it. Once you step back, you know,
我也喜歡  當你后退一步的時候
and you kind of let the folksy layers--
就好像你讓這些層次變得平易近人了
You rang?
你叫我嗎
Agnes, please meet our guests.
艾格尼絲  認識一下我們的客人
Agnes.
艾格尼絲
Ah, she's a bit like Master Po from Kung Fu.
她有點像《功夫熊貓》里的阿寶
Is that okay? Good.
這樣可以嗎  好的
Hi Peter, I'm Morgan.
你好彼得  我是茉根
Hello.
你好
Marie and I met backpacking across Devon.
瑪麗和我在德文郡徒步旅行時相遇
Bonded over the last bag of trail mix and here I am.
吃完最后一袋混合干果  我就過來了
Supplementing the nups with a touch of class.
用高雅的品味來豐富我的婚禮
- Touch. - Oh, that's nice.
-高雅  -這挺好的
I bet you've got tons of that
我猜你一定得到了許多
despite your--your fragile stature.
盡管你的身材很脆弱
Lovely home.
很溫馨的家
Thank you.
謝謝你
Architecturally speaking.
從建筑上說
Style wise, I can't say I really care for it.
就風格而言  我不能說我真的喜歡
Muddled at best.
充其量算混亂
First of all, this house is stupid.
首先  這房子蠢極了
Second, are you gonna feed us or what, papi?
其次  你打不打算給我們吃的
Because you don't want to see me hangry.
因為你一定不想看見我饑餓的樣子
It's all you guys.
都是你們
I can't.
我不行
This little things are delicious.
這小東西很好吃
All right.
好了
I've gotta Instagram this.
我要把這發到照片墻上
And, um, I'm gonna get, like,
我會弄一些
chair covers.
椅子套
They're called chair cozies.
那叫椅子保溫罩
No, no, wedding chair cozies can't look great.
不不  婚禮椅子保溫罩肯定很難看
Fuckin' bean bags would be better.
豆袋坐墊更好
Do I look like Meghan Markle to y'all?
在你們眼里我像梅格漢·馬克爾[英國王妃]嗎
I mean, that's why you should just have the wedding in,
這就是你為什么應該把婚禮
like, a barn of something.
開在谷倉里的原因
- A barn? - But not, like, an actual barn.
-谷倉  -不  不是真正的谷倉
Oh my God, forget I said anything.
我的天  忘了我剛才說的
Peter, how do you feel about wedding chair cozies?
彼得  你怎么看待婚禮椅子保溫套的
- Me? Uh, well... - Yeah.
-我嗎  -是的
...to be honest with you guys,
實話跟你們說
I have no idea what the gentle fuck you're talkin' about.
我根本不知道你們在說些什么
I want to know more though.
但我想知道一下
I want to know more. Keep sharing.
我想知道更多  繼續說吧
For those of you willing,
如果你們愿意的話
what you're about to enjoy...
你們接下來要享用的
is a pan-seared monkfish.
是煎安康魚
You'll see some English peas.
你們將會看到一些英國豌豆
Those are fresh.
很新鮮
Oh my gosh, this is beautiful.
天啊  太好看了
I mean, it looks like cod.
看起來像是鱈魚
There's a similarity.
它們有相似點
Uh, Elena,
艾琳娜
but, um, it's much higher end.
但是它更高端一些
Y'all, eat up, eat up also,
吃吧  吃吧
because this is super expensive at his restaurant.
因為這在他的飯店里很貴
The reason I broke up with him mainly
我和他分手的主要原因是
was because he thought he got to decide
因為他覺得他有權決定
when and if I had babies.
我要不要以及什么時候要孩子
But also the salt, no?
還有鹽  對嗎
Also he salted his bacon.
他連培根都要腌制
Oh, that's always gross.
這太難吃了
- Fuck no. - Yeah, it was grim.
-不是吧  -確實很惡心
But it wasn't as bad as the man I loved
但我愛的人想要決定
wanting to determine
我的身體什么時候改變
when my body transforms and bursts forth with...
什么時候有新生命從我身體里破殼而出
- suckling young. - Goodness gracious,
-這樣也不壞  -我的天哪
you make it sound like the last act of Akira, Morgan.
你說得好像是《阿基拉》的最后一幕  茉根
It's not that bad.
也沒有那么糟
I'm sorry, Peter, have you birthed many children?
抱歉  彼得  你有過孩子嗎
Um, I haven't, unfortunately,
很遺憾  我還沒有
but I did see it happen.
但我見過別人生孩子
Listen, I saw it happen up close and personal,
我親自近距離目睹過
and I feel like if I had the gadgetry,
我感覺如果我有那個小玩意
I would have delivered.
我會要孩子的
The gadgetry, you guys.
小玩意  大伙兒
You know, it's not just the delivery, right?
不只是生孩子  對嗎
It's everything that comes next
是接下來發生的一切
and then everything after that.
和在那之后的一切
You're right, I'm sorry, I forgot that you managed
你說得對  抱歉  我忘了你想辦法
to avoid the pushing part,
略去了分娩的部分
which is so sweet for you, it's rad.
你真是太好了  很棒
But I'm also a fan of adoption, so...
但我也接受領養  所以...
No, I was just saying I don't think raising a child
我只是說  我不覺得撫養一個小孩
should be another thing we have to prioritize, you know?
應該是我們需要優先考慮的一個事
It's not a burden or a task,
這不是負擔或是任務
it's just simply what is.
只是很簡單的一件事
Becomes as much part of your life as breathing.
就像呼吸一樣  只是你生活的一部分
But then the parts of your life
但你生活的一部分
that you thought were your life,
你之前覺得是你的生活
like socializing or career building,
比如社交或是創業
and, you know, exploring or expressing art,
探索及表達藝術
those things that drove you and defined you,
這些事驅動你  定義你
all those boxes get left unchecked.
所有的這些選項都沒被選中
Of course they still matter.
當然他們還是很重要
And you want your child to grow up
你們希望你的孩子長大之后
and see more than just Mom.
不僅僅是想當一名母親
You want them to see a dreamer and a lover
你想讓他們成為一名夢想家或是愛人
and an entrepreneur or whatever.
或是企業家之類的
You want them to see...
你想讓他們成為
you.
你
And maybe be inspired.
或許會受到鼓舞
Oh my God, when is Mother's Day, May?
我的天  母親節是什么時候  五月嗎
Fuck.
該死
I see you.
我成為了你
I love you.
我愛你
Well, that is a cockle warmer.
這真是溫馨的一幕
No, nothing?
沒感覺嗎
Tough room.
氣氛很僵硬啊
Guys, come on, I'm kidding.
各位  拜托  我開玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我開玩笑的
That was a beautiful soliloquy, Lilith,
這是一段美妙的獨白  莉莉絲
and I think that we should all drink to it.
我覺得我們應該為此喝一杯
Oh my God, Peter.
我的天  彼得
Oh my goshness.
我的老天
I've just embarrassed myself.
我讓自己變得尷尬了
- Well--well caught. - It's okay.
-幸虧你抓住了  -沒事的
I'm also very curious
我也很好奇
as to what is-- what is that about?
這是什么東西
That's intriguing.
這有點吸引我
What this is about?
這是什么
Sisterhood.
姐妹情誼
Celtic style, am I right, ladies?
凱爾特風格  我說的對嗎女士們
It was about Mardi Gras 2015.
那是2015年的狂歡節
Year of the motherfuckin' goat.
當時是羊年
Oh, I love our tattoos.
我喜歡我們的紋身
Yeah, me too.
我也是
Oh, whoa, is anybody else sweating like they stole something?
天啊  有人也出汗嗎  像偷了東西一樣
Elena, how are you hot?
艾琳娜  你怎么這么熱
- I don't know. - She always is.
-我不知道  -她總是這樣
*Go to sleep*
*去睡覺吧*
*Underneath the cover*
*在掩蓋之下*
See anything out there you like?
外面有你喜歡的嗎
Well, uh, speaking man to matron,
作為雇主對女傭說
I-- I could say
我可以說
there's nothing out there I don't like.
外面沒有我不喜歡的
How inclusive of you.
你可真是包容啊
Thank you.
謝謝你
Truthfully, though,
但是實話實說
I am feeling kind of invisible to housewares.
我感覺我有點不會使用廚具了
Huh, wiser words without slurring might help.
明智而不含糊其辭的話可能會有所幫助
Maybe stop spilling shit.
或許別再瞎說八道了
Your honesty is boundary free, Ags.
你的誠實沒有底線  艾格尼絲
And I am tipsy.
而我是真的醉了
Eat something, for Christ's sake.
天啊  吃點東西吧
Well, sure.
好
Go easy, I'm not gonna clean up any more of your messes.
悠著點  我不會替你收拾你的爛攤子了
- Here. - Thank you.
-給你  -謝謝你
Thank you, mm, reheated.
謝謝你  又加熱了一遍
BTDubs, I'm a big fan of you and your porridge.
順便說一句  我很喜歡你和你的粥
- I like that. - Yeah, thanks.
-我喜歡  -謝了
Yeah, when is the last time you had a solid girls' night out?
你上次正經和姑娘們一起瀟灑是什么時候了
I feel like you should get out there,
我覺得你該出去
tell 'em some shit about Eleanor Roosevelt,
告訴她們關于埃莉諾·羅斯福的八卦
you know what I'm saying?
你懂我的意思嗎
Maybe tell 'em the story of the first vacuum.
也許跟她們說說第一個吸塵器的故事
You're an idiot.
你真是個傻子
*Underneath the cover*
*面具之下*
That's-- that's gorgeous.
真是太好聽了
Anybody need cream or milk?
誰想要奶油或牛奶
Just let me know.
就告訴我
My gosh, Agnes!
我的天  艾格尼絲
You've been on your feet all day.
你都忙一天了
Why don't you sit down, take a load off?
不如你坐會歇歇
Maybe drop some knowledge.
也許傳授點知識
I'm too old to be dropping anything.
我太老了  傳授什么都不好使了
I'm just enjoying the festivities watching some sisters commune.
我只是很享受看到姐妹們團聚
Oh, there she is.
她來了
Suffrage.
選舉權
My day.
我的最愛
No? Okay.
都不喜歡嗎  好吧
Truth is, you all are lucky.
其實你們都很幸運
Wasn't always this easy for women to lean on each other.
女人互相依靠并不是件易事
There was a time when it...
在那個時代
wasn't about choosing to be heard,
沒有人在意女人的心聲
because you had no voice.
因為你無法發聲
How can you use something you were never given?
如果不曾擁有  又如何使用
Something terrible happens to a woman and it just lives in you.
女人遭受的痛苦都會在你們心中留下烙印
In her.
在她心中
Starts on the inside and then it becomes her skin
首先侵蝕你的內心  然后蔓延至皮膚
and she wears it till she dies and that's that.
直到她死去  都會留有印記
And that was just her tight five, ladies.
剛才她只是在熱身  姑娘們
Wait, just wait until her Hulu special drops this fall.
等著看今年秋天Hulu臺特別節目上映吧
I made chocolate things for women.
我為女士們做了巧克力
- Please don't all just... - I'm good, bro.
-請別一下子...  -謝了  老兄
- Yeah. - Maybe later, Peter. Thanks.
-好  -也許等會吧  謝了  彼得
They look like wild flavors.
看上去像野花
Oh, yeah. Yes.
對  沒錯
You all right over there, Pete?
你還好嗎  彼得
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
還行
I just-- I maybe had a little too much to drink
我就是  也許酒喝多了
and not enough to eat.
吃的太少
This is the-- this is the chef's curse.
這就是  就是廚師的詛咒
Hey, I'll bid you excuse me.
恕我失陪一下
I'll bid you adieu.
恕我不奉陪
Um, stay as long as you like, okay?
你們想待多久都行
Stay the night if you like.
如果愿意可以住下來
I will be available for some light spooning during the witching hour,
午夜時分我可以來點側臥相擁
as long as I can be the big spoon.
只要我可以做外側的那個人
Peter, your hospitality is greatly appreciated.
彼得  很感謝你的好意
Thank you and Agnes for such a delicious meal.
謝謝你和艾格尼絲做的美味晚餐
I had this gravity.
我有重力
There's a step there.
那里有臺階
- Good night. - Okay.
-晚安  -好
Thank you.
謝謝
Cheerio.
你好啊
Well, that's good.
幸好還活著
Hey, how much did we drink?
我們喝了多少酒
Okay.
好吧
*There were two sisters side by side*
*兩個姐妹肩并肩*
*Sing aye dumb, sing aye day*
*唱吧傻瓜  整日吟唱*
*The boys are born for me*
*這些男孩為我而生*
*There were two sisters side by side*
*兩個姐妹肩并肩*
*The eldest for young Johnny cried*
*愛哭小約翰和姐姐一對*
Okay, I'll bite.
行  我去看看
*I'll be true unto my love*
*我會對愛人忠心不二*
*If he'll be true to me*
*若他對我真心*
*Johnny bought the youngest a big gold ring*
*約翰給妹妹買了一個大金戒*
*Sing aye dumb, sing aye day*
*唱吧傻瓜  整日吟唱*
*The boys are born for me*
*這些男孩為我而生*
Well, hey there, Glorio.
你好啊  格洛里奧
I do like your outfit, but...
我喜歡你的外套  但是
why are you here?
你在這干什么
Are you a boarder
你是來借宿
or are you just visiting Agnes?
還是只是探望艾格尼絲
I'm gonna turn that down
我去把那個關了
'cause it sucks.
因為太難聽
*If he'll be true to me*
*若他對我真心*
*Johnny bought the youngest a beaver hat*
*約翰為妹妹買了頂海貍帽*
*Sing aye dumb*♪
*唱吧傻瓜*
Sh...
天
Fuck no.
不
Hey Morgan, rise and shine, please.
茉根  太陽照屁股了
Fuck!
操
I'm pretty sure that Agnes
我很確定艾格尼絲
worships peacocks and the devil.
崇拜孔雀和魔鬼
Morgan, is that you?
茉根  是你嗎
Peter, help me.
彼得  幫幫我
Morgan!
茉根
Goddammit.
該死
False!
見鬼
Morgan, pull--pull on your side of the door, please.
茉根  從你那邊拉門
I'm pulling.
我在拉
Morgan?
茉根
Open the goddamned door!
快開門
I can't, it's locked!
我開不了  鎖上了
Peter, help me, I'm scared.
彼得  幫幫我  我好害怕
Oh, shit!
該死
Peter? Are you still there?
彼得  你還在嗎
Morgan, something's wrong.
茉根  有點不對勁
I can't move!
我動不了
Morgan, wake up!
茉根  醒醒
I think I'm paralyzed.
我覺得我癱瘓了
Oh, God... Peter.
天哪  彼得
Where am I?
我在哪
Look at me. No, no, no.
看著我  不不
Look at, look at-- do not turn around.
看著我  看我  別回頭
Oh my God.
我的天
Oh my... oh my God!
天哪  我的天
What?
什么
Peter, Peter, pumpkin eater.
彼得  彼得  愛吃南瓜
Had a wife but couldn't keep her,
家有嬌妻卻留不住她
because he'd been a very, very bad boy.
因為他是個調皮的壞男孩
What the fuck?
什么情況
Well-done, Morgan.
干得好  茉根
No, I think I can probably take it from here.
不  接下來交給我吧
Stiff upper lip, mate.
堅強點  哥們
It's been a deuce of a time.
真是段倒霉的日子
- Thank you. - Thank you.
-謝謝  -謝謝你
Peter.
彼得
I just can't imagine
我沒法想象
what's running through your head right now.
現在你心里的想法
Oh, you don't need to, I can tell you, it's, uh,
無需想像  我可以直接告訴你
"Why can't I move my fuckin' body"
"為什么我他媽的動不了"
and "Get this collar off me fuckin' now."
還有"趕緊把這個項圈從我脖子上摘了"
Language!
別爆粗口
Who do you think you are?
你以為自己是誰
Who do you think I am?
我以為自己是誰
I'd say I'm surprised you don't recognize me, Peter,
我很意外你沒認出我  彼得
but to be fair, I was a child the last time you were around.
但說實話  上次見你時我還是個孩子
Still, everyone says I'm the spitting image of my sister, and, well,
不過大家都說  我和我姐長得一模一樣
I know you remember her.
我知道你肯定記得她
I have no idea who you're talking about.
我完全不知道你在說什么
Wheeler.
惠勒
Kara Wheeler.
卡拉·惠勒
You're Becca's sister?
你是貝卡的妹妹
Was.
曾是
So that's what all this insanity is about.
原來這些瘋狂舉動都是為了她
She took the easy way out.
她是自殺的
It's my fault?
這還是我的錯
What happened to your sister is tragic.
你姐姐的死是一場悲劇
Truly.
真的
It's also fuckin' cowardly.
也非常懦弱
Right? What about your parents?
不是嗎  你的父母怎么辦
What about you?
你怎么辦
And then the heroin.
還有海洛因
The fuckin' heroin, Kara.
海洛因  卡拉
Come on, I know you're angry.
拜托  我知道你很生氣
You want some closure, but this,
你想要些安慰  但這個
this is not the way to get it.
這樣你得不到慰藉
This... this is how you get 10 to 20.
這樣你將面臨十到二十年的牢獄之災
Did you know I was the one that found her?
你知道是我發現了她的尸體嗎
She used a knife from your line of cutlery, Peter.
她用了你的烹飪刀  彼得
The very set you sell on your piece-of-shit TV show.
就是在你的狗屁電視節目上出售的那種
Do you think that was a coincidence?
你以為那是個巧合嗎
We were teenagers, okay, Kara?
當時我們只是青少年  卡拉
And whatever you're thinking,
無論你以為發生了什么
fuck, I guarantee you
該死  我保證
that's not what happened, all right?
事情不是那樣  好嗎
Right on cue.
時間正好
- All right. - Shit.
-好樣的  -該死
Okay.
好
Uh, what the hell is that?
那是什么玩意
Don't worry, it's not loaded.
別擔心  還沒裝上弓呢
Right, then, now that it's loaded,
現在裝上了
I would be worried, if I were you.
如果我是你  我就會擔心
What the fuck?
什么玩意
Holy shit.
我了個去
You seem tense, Peter.
你看上去很緊張  彼得
Way to represent, OG.
說得好  老大
Suckling young.
這樣也不壞
Oh my God.
天啊
Okay, okay, okay, so you are all crazy,
好吧  你們都是瘋子
you're all just crazy,
你們都瘋了
and your brains are sick,
你們的大腦有問題
and you're not gonna get away with this,
你們會因此受到懲罰的
you... angry bitches!
你們這些憤怒的婊子
Oh, Peter.
彼得
We're not angry bitches.
我們不是憤怒的婊子
We're angry witches.
我們是憤怒的女巫
Agnes!
艾格尼絲
What did you do to me?
你對我做了什么
The paralysis.
癱瘓
It's a remedial spell but always quite effective.
這是個補充咒  但總是很有效
Now, if you'll excuse me, Peter,
容我失陪一下  彼得
a woman's work is never, ever done.
一個女人總有很多事要做
Agnes!
艾格尼絲
Help me!
救救我
Have some self-respect, Slim.
給自己留點自尊  小瘦子
What are you...
你們在干什...
What are you planning?
你們在計劃什么
Hey, what is your deal, even... huh?
你們怎么回事
Yeah? What is that-- what is that--
那是什么  那是什么
what is that nonverbal cue, huh?
你們剛才交換的那個眼神
You guys aren't helping me at all, please.
你們根本沒在幫我
We can't let you go out like this.
我們不能讓你這樣出來
Out?
出門
Don't sweat it.
別害怕
We're gonna tighten you up.
我們要打理一下你
You're gonna tighten me up,
你們要幫我打理
what is tighten-- tighten what up?
什么打理  打理什么
All of it.
所有一切
Oh, come on.
拜托
Shh, stay very still.
別動
No! No, no, this stops now.
不  不不  不能這樣了
*Shut, shut, shut, shut*
*閉嘴閉嘴閉嘴閉嘴*
*Shut your fucking mouth*
*閉上你的臭嘴*
*No one wants to hear your bullshit*
*沒人想聽你的廢話*
- No! No. - Oh, boy.
-不  不  -天哪
That's good.
不錯
No.
不
Oh, God.
天哪
Oh, f...
操
Oh, shit!
該死
Snake for snake.
毒蛇給蛇蝎
You don't even know me.
你們都不認識我
You don't know me, all you know is
你們不認識我  你們只知道
what you read in the search engine.
搜索引擎里讀到的那些
Thank you so much for this exclusive.
非常感謝能給我這個獨家采訪
Confession? I'm a big fan,
說實話  我是你的忠實粉絲
But this is just business.
但這采訪只是工作
Well, flattery'll get you everywhere.
阿諛奉承能給你開很多門
My business is my pleasure.
我的工作就是我的快樂之源
What is this?
這是什么
- Um... great. - Yeah!
-好極了  -沒錯
So let's get started, okay.
那我們開始吧
When did your love affair
你與食物
with food start?
何時結下了情緣
Why don't you ask me what you really wanna ask me?
不如你直接問我你真正想問的問題
I don't know what you mean.
我不知道你什么意思
Okay, fuck no, you guys, come on.
好吧  我操了  別這樣
You're family, for Christ's sake.
你們是一家人  老天
This is wrong on so many levels, what it--
這簡直錯得太離譜了  怎么
what is happening?
怎么回事
Oh-- oh please, can we just,
別  我們能不能
stick to the interview?
能不能就專注采訪
Come on, this is the interview.
別裝了  這就是采訪
Look, I--I...
聽著  我...
can we just keep it on the level?
我們能不能專業點
- Yeah, yeah. - I'm really not comfortable
-好啊  -我真的不喜歡
- with where this is-- - Okay, okay, hey.
-你這樣...  -好吧好吧
Seriously?
真的嗎
How long you been chasing this exclusive?
你爭取這個獨家新聞多久了
I mean, who the fuck do you write for?
你到底寫給誰看
Who's reading this shit? Come on.
有誰讀你這玩意  拜托
No, no, no, no, you assholes.
不不  你們這些混蛋
I'm your brass ring. I'm your brass ring.
我是你成名的機會  我是你成名的機會
No, that's not how it happened.
不不  事情不是這樣的
That's not how it happened.
事情不是這樣的
This-- can you please cut that out?
你們能不能消停會
Cut--cut that out.
別演了
Ow! Cunt!
賤人
You fucking bit me!
你他媽咬了我
Unquote.
暫停
She don't wanna fuck you, Peter.
她根本不想和你上床  彼得
Just because she's a fan of your work
雖然她是你的粉絲
doesn't mean you get to touch her.
但不意味著你能碰她
Here, or here...
這里  或者這里
It's not okay.
不可以
It's never been okay.
從來都不可以
Look at the tits.
看看奶子
Check the tits, bro.
看看奶子  兄弟
Hey, how about a giant obvious newsflash
不如我告訴你們瘋女人
for you two certifiable loony bins:
一個顯而易見的道理
There's two sides to every story, okay?
每個故事都有兩面  懂嗎
She chased that exclusive for weeks.
她為了這個獨家新聞爭取了好幾周
- She met me at a bar. - You told her to meet you there!
-她在酒吧和我見面  -是你讓她去的
She brought a recorder
她帶了一個錄音筆
and a fucking legal pad!
和一個筆記薄
She flirted her ass off with me the whole time.
一整晚她都在拼命和我調情
And then, she had the balls to bite me,
之后她竟然還有膽咬我
because she was a crazy bitch!
因為她就是個瘋婆子
You wanna see something really fucking crazy?
你想見識下真正瘋狂的東西嗎
Oh boy.
老天
What's happening?
怎么回事
You pissed off a witch, Peter.
你惹女巫生氣了  彼得
- And Marie fucks with voodoo, so... - Oh, shit.
-而且瑪麗還是伏都教  所以  -該死
Oh God. Oh God, help me. Please, please help me.
天哪  天哪  救救我  救救我吧
Not yet, Marie.
還不行  瑪麗
It's too soon.
時候未到
- He fucking asked for it. - I have no doubt.
-他自找的  -我知道
You are officially on borrowed time.
你現在是真的時日無多了
Oh boy, look at that.
天哪  快看
Look what you did.
看看你干的好事
You pissed yourself.
你尿床了
Now you're gonna have to lay there in your own sauce
現在你只能躺在自己的尿里
and I'm gonna have to smell it.
而我還得聞著
Still, you're lucky.
但你還是很幸運
I wouldn't have stopped her.
我本不會阻止她
All that spitfire just makes me melt.
她的烈性子簡直讓我神魂顛倒
Why do you think I asked her to marry me?
不然我為什么向她求婚呢
She checks all my boxes.
她就是我的夢中情人
- That is disgusting. - Oh, I'm sorry.
-真惡心  -不好意思
Is that a bridge too far?
這個對你來說太重口了嗎
Oh, shit! So it's just all lies, huh?
該死  所以一切都是謊言嗎
God, you don't even have a kid.
天哪  你都沒有孩子
Don't be ridiculous.
別傻了
My daughter graduated cum laude last year,
我女兒去年以優異成績畢業
and that was after the assault.
還是在那次襲擊之后
Luckily, that monster was still able to play in a bowl game.
幸運的是  那個禽獸還能如魚得水
Hasn't seemed to have affected his draft status one bit.
絲毫沒有受到任何影響
Thank God she had the courage to come forward.
感謝上帝她有勇氣站出來
What are you thinking?
你在想什么
There we go.
給你敷上
Stick around for act two.
等待第二幕
That's when we castrate you.
到那時我們再閹了你
No peeking!
不準偷看
¡Hola!
你好啊
That's a nice--
真是個
that's a nice color.
這顏色真不錯
Oh, I'm so glad you like it!
我很高興你喜歡
We thought it would look good with your skin tone.
我們覺得這顏色很配你的膚色
You ready to become Pretty Peter?
你準備好變身為漂亮彼得了嗎
Are you excited to head back to the Philippines in shackles?
你準備好戴著手銬腳鏈回菲律賓了嗎
Wow. This motherfucker-- you know I'm Puerto Rican!
這個混球  你知道我是波多黎各人
You wanna talk about shackles?
你想談談手銬嗎
You know, when Puerto Rico was still a Spanish colony,
當波多黎各還是西班牙殖民地時
women's rights were unheard of
根本沒有女權這一說
and their contributions to the island's society were limited,
而她們對島上的社會貢獻非常受限
to put it mildly.
委婉地說
Even though Puerto Rican women were actively participating
盡管波多黎各女人積極參與
in the revolt against the Spaniards,
反抗西班牙人
and nobody can rape and pillage like the Spanish,
但沒人比西班牙人更擅長強奸和掠奪
am I right?
不是嗎
Relax.
放松
I'm just texturizing.
我在給你上妝
- Will you pout, please? - Will you eat a dick?
-你能撅嘴嗎  -你能食屌嗎
That's rude.
好粗魯
Believe it or not,
信不信由你
I'm as American as apple-motherfucking-pie.
我可是個正宗的美國人
My great-grandmother served our great country
我的曾祖母為國而戰
in the war against Hitler and his allies.
與希特勒和他的盟軍打仗
What a patriot!
多么愛國啊
I'm sorry that the courage skipped your generation.
我很抱歉這份勇氣沒遺傳給你
But I am grateful for her service, truly.
但我感激她的奉獻  真的
Are you?
是嗎
The way you're grateful for the service of,
就像你很感激
I don't know, your female kitchen staff?
你的女性員工的付出嗎
You ever hear of equal pay for equal work,
你聽說過同工同酬嗎
you pasty piece of shit?
你這個垃圾
And how many of them have you slept with, huh?
你睡過多少個手下
Including the one you fired.
包括你開除的那個
Marta Dominguez.
瑪塔·多明戈斯
Single mother of two,
單親媽媽  兩個孩子
and that was enough brown babies for this world,
不過在你看來  這個世界已經有
as far as you were concerned.
夠多的棕色寶寶了
Yeah, we came to that decision together.
這是我們共同的決定
Together?
共同
Then why settle?
那為什么要給封口費
That one cost you 20 grand.
你給了她兩萬吧
Big money for one of your employees.
為一個員工花這么多錢可是大手筆
Isn't this beneath you, Morgan?
你不該這樣做吧  茉根
Didn't you people invent manners?
你們不是發明禮儀的嗎
He means the English.
他是說英國
None of this shit flies across the Pond.
這些都不是從那兒傳過來的
This is strictly American awfulness at its worst.
這些都是美式最下作的手段
First of all, Peter,
首先  彼得
the utter shite that you've been doing
你這輩子做的下作事
your entire life is part of an international pandemic.
基本堪比全球性的霍亂了
- Ooh, good word. - Yeah. And second,
-說得好  -第二
do you know a thing about fuckin' witchcraft
你知道該死的巫術
and its fuckin' origins?
和該死的起源嗎
Nice. Come on, I'm... trying to talk to you like a human,
拜托  我...我想和你進行正常的交流
and you're mocking me and you're wrapping your finger
但你卻嘲諷我  還想個惡霸一樣
around a trigger like a bully.
把手指扣在扳機上
You're a real wanker when you're frightened,
你害怕的時候真的很無能
do you know that?
你知道嗎
Yeah, I'm frightened, Morgan.
我的確很害怕  茉根
I'm scared, 'cause I've been kidnapped and...
我很害怕  因為我被綁架了  而且
accused,
被陌生人
and convicted and sentenced by strangers, and I--
指控  定罪  處刑  我...
I have a daughter named Riley.
我有一個叫萊利的女兒
Yeah, but Peter,
但是  彼得
great change comes with the destruction of existing rules.
摧毀現有的規則就會帶來巨大的改變
What?
什么
My sister's skin is my own,
我妹妹的皮膚和我一樣
my sister's heart is my own,
我妹妹的心和我一樣
and my sister's future is my own.
我妹妹的未來和我一樣
Oh, shit, she's in training, huh?
該死  她還是個新人
This is your first time, isn't it?
這是你第一次  對嗎
In your dreams.
做夢去吧
No, not in my dreams, right now.
不  我現在可不是做夢
I know you.
我了解你
I grew up with you.
我和你一起長大
Morgan.
茉根
You're just like my sister.
你就像是我的妹妹
You're desperate for acceptance.
你渴望被人所接受
I have a brother.
我有個哥哥
He makes cheese-and-onion sandwiches
他會做奶酪洋蔥三明治
and they're the tits.
他們就愛到發狂
You still couldn't shine his shoes.
他的鞋子就是擦不亮
Who was it that destroyed your self-esteem so completely
是誰摧毀了你的自尊
that you are willing
讓你愿意
to pledge the worst sorority in history?
加入有史以來都爛的姐妹會
Was it your dad?
是你爸爸嗎
That's enough, pendejo.
夠了  蠢蛋
Every asshole says he's an asshole
每個混蛋都會說
because his father was an asshole.
因為爸爸是混蛋所以自己才變成混蛋
No te dejes que te meta en la cabeza.
別被他的話迷惑了
It's just dead skin.
這只是他的把戲
Morgan, come on.
茉根  拜托
Make one decision for yourself
這輩子為你自己
- in your life. - Fuck you!
-決定一次  -操你媽的
You know nothing about my life!
你對我的這輩子一點都不了解
Welcome to the fucking game, bitch!
歡迎加入我們  賤人
Oh, shit!
該死
Star... six... nine.
星號  六  九
- Hello? - Lonnie-- Lonnie, it's Peter.
-喂  -朗尼  我是彼得
I'm a hostage of witches.
我被女巫們綁架了
I tried 911 already, it's busy, can you believe--
我報過警了  打不通  你能相信...
You just made this a lot more painful for yourself, Peter.
你這樣只會讓你自己更痛苦  彼得
Lonnie?
朗尼
That's my name, don't wear it out.
我是叫這個名字  別忘了
God, it's so late, you freaked me out there
天啊  這么晚了  你真是
for a second.
嚇了我一跳
Right.
沒錯
I don't live here.
我不住在這里的
Peter invited us ladies over for dinner.
彼得邀請我們幾位女士來共進晚餐
Our power went out and he took pity on us.
我們沒電了  他可憐我們
Peter called me at the shop,
彼得給我店里打了個電話
he sounded pretty shook up.
他聽起來很驚慌
Lonnie, Peter's fine.
朗尼  彼得沒事
He was just yanking your chain.
他只是騙你的
Like when we were kids?
就像我們小時候那樣
- Oh, but we're not kids anymore. - He was a bully, Lonnie.
-但是我們不是小孩子了  -他是個惡霸  朗尼
I'm sorry if he ever made you feel like you were--
我很遺憾  他之前一直都讓你覺得你...
Dumb?
很蠢嗎
- I'm not dumb. - I know you're not.
-我不蠢  -我知道
Hmm, you probably should turned more lights on,
如果你真的指望我相信
if you really wanted me to believe
你們在里面共進晚餐
that you were inside having supper.
那你們最好多開點燈
I'll come in and take a look around.
我要進去看一看
Lonnie...
朗尼
Go home, boy.
回家吧  孩子
- This doesn't concern you. - Mother...
-這與你無關  -母親
I got this handled, go on back to bed.
交給我吧  回床上去
What did I tell you about that thing, huh?
我和你怎么說的來著
What'd I say?
我怎么說的
Something's not right here.
這里有點不對勁
- You love your mother? - 'Course I do.
-你愛你的母親嗎  -當然了
All right.
好吧
Then you take this and you go home.
那就收好這個  回家
Everything's under control.
一切都在掌控之中
You just forget you were ever here.
你忘記你自己來過這里
Your timing is impeccable.
你出現的時機正好
Does Peter know?
彼得知道嗎
Peter and Gwen were just babies themselves.
彼得和格溫自己當時都只是孩子
Why'd you have to keep it a secret?
你為什么要保守這個秘密
Because the apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
因為蘋果不會落到離樹很遠的地方
Oh my God.
天啊
Peter's father?
彼得的父親
Go back in there and finish what you started.
回去了結你自己挑起的事
And no more fuck-ups.
不要再搞砸了
Hey, man. What the fuck?
伙計  搞什么
That was enlightening.
這可不大好
Gimme the keys, I'll take care of it.
把鑰匙給我  交給我
I'll call shotgun.
獵槍給我
None of that will be necessary.
這都沒必要
Oh, oh, really?
真的嗎
Tell that to my fucking forehead.
跟我的額頭說去
We should've cast a stronger spell.
我們應該施更強的咒語
We actually underestimated you.
我們低估了你
Crate training's over.
籠內訓練結束了
Oh, cuckoo, cuckoo!
布谷  布谷
- What a beautiful color. - Yeah, I like the way
-這配色真不錯  -我喜歡
your titties look in that top, baby.
你穿這件衣服后立起來的奶頭  寶貝
Look, really?
有必要嗎
Your sister's clothes?
穿你妹妹的衣服
I mean, isn't she rolling in her grave?
她不是已經入土了嗎
We're going on a witch hunt.
我們要進行女巫捕獵
You get it? Levels.
你懂嗎  層次不一樣
It's really more of us hunting you
應該是我們來捕獵你
as opposed to you hunting us.
而不是你捕獵我們
It's a twist on an old classic.
對經典的反轉
Vámonos, gringo. -
走吧  外國佬
Come on, jog on!
來  跑吧
Go, Pe-ter!
快跑  彼得
Can I just shoot him in the bollocks?
我能直接射他嗎
- Go Peter, go! Oh! Come on!
-快跑  彼得  -拜托
Please, please.
拜托  拜托
Please stop this. She had a soul.
不要這樣  她的在天之靈看著呢
- Ten... - You better run, boy.
-十  -你還是快跑吧  小伙子
Hey! Okay, sorry.
好吧  抱歉
Nine...
九
- Okay. - Eight...
-好吧  -八
- Go Peter, go! - Seven...
-快跑  彼得  -七
Sh-- shit.
該死
Marta Dominguez.
瑪塔·多明戈斯
She don't wanna fuck you...
她根本不想和你上床  彼得
Peter.
彼得
We were teenagers,
當時我們只是青少年
okay?
好嗎
Help! Help!
救命  救命
Help me!
救救我
Help me! Hel-- Oh, shit!
救命  該死
Gwen! Gwen! Gwen! Wait!
格溫  格溫  等等
- Oh thank God, it's you! - Peter, what is--
-謝天謝地  是你  -彼得  怎么...
Fuck! Go, go, go!
該死  快走  快走
- Peter, what-- - Fuckin' drive, Gwen, fuckin' drive!
-彼得  你...  -快開車  格溫  快開
- Okay, okay! - Shit!
-好吧  -該死
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
你要告訴我是怎么回事嗎
What the hell are you wearing?
你穿的是什么東西
Fuckin' bitch witches tortured me.
有一群女巫折磨我
Fuckin' took me hostage.
她們綁架了我
The put a spell on my limbs, Gwen!
她們給我的腿施法  格溫
Goddamn, they took my hair,
該死  她們剪去了我的頭發
took my blood.
取走了我的血
They put makeup on my face, look at my face!
她們在我臉上化妝  盯著我的臉
Slow down, okay? Just--
慢點  好嗎  你...
I can't slow down, Gwen.
我沒法慢點  格溫
They're blaming me for Becca's suicide.
她們把貝卡的自殺怪在我頭上
Yeah.
對
You know Kara, her sister?
你知道卡拉嗎  她的妹妹
Well, she's the lady Manson, she's the ringleader.
她就是女殺人魔  她是領頭的
And they've been following me,
她們一直在跟蹤我
and they know some deep, deep personal secrets.
她們知道我的一些非常非常深的秘密
They're stalking me and we need to go,
她們正在跟蹤我  我們得趕緊走
and we need to go to the cops now.
我們得趕緊去找警察
Oh, fuck!
操
They were gonna cut my dick off.
她們要把我的屌切了
I said they could fix you, not "Fix" You.
她們會修復好你  不是解決你
What in the living shit did you just say to me?
你剛剛說什么
You heard me.
你聽得很清楚
You did this to me?
這都是你干的
- Gwen-- - I didn't want to!
-格溫  -我也不想的
Okay? But you just-- you left me no choice,
好嗎  但是你讓我別無選擇
because it's happening all over again, and--
因為歷史又一次重演了
Oh yeah, you better be upset.
沒錯  你繼續難受吧
'Cause you have scarred me for life
因為你讓我留下了一輩子的陰影
and you are my goddamned sister!
你可是我的妹妹
Yeah, I was your sister when you raped my best friend
沒錯  你就是在我們的樹屋里
in our fucking treehouse!
強奸了我最好的朋友
Rape? Did you just say "Rape" To me?
強奸  你說我"強奸"
Holy shit, Gwen, I don't even know
上帝啊  格溫  我都不知道
what that fuckin' word means anymore.
這個詞到底是什么意思
Nobody does, okay?
沒有人知道  好嗎
We were kids.
我們當時還是孩子
I was a teenager, I was drunk,
我才十幾歲  我喝醉了
I was fuckin' naked, it was a blurry mess
我光著身子  那感覺都是上輩子的事了
that happened a lifetime ago!
一片模糊
No, it's a blurry mess to you, Peter.
不  對你來說是一片模糊  彼得
It's a lifetime ago to you!
對你來說是上輩子的事
- Like I said, I was drunk. - No!
-我說了  我醉了  -不
No, you always have an excuse, Peter,
不  你永遠有借口  彼得
and you always get away with it,
你永遠能逃脫
and it is not just with Becca,
不僅僅是貝卡
because there have been too many others,
因為還有太多其他受害者
what about the journalist that interviewed you
那個幾年前
a few years ago, right? Hm, what did you do to her?
采訪你的記者呢  你對她做了什么
Huh, Peter? Or the women on your staff,
彼得  或者你的那個員工
or the new one that your lawyer's
或者你的律師
fixing for you right now, what were the--
最近在給你處理的那個
what were the marching orders this time?
這次的辭退令是怎么寫的
Is it "Oh, she auditioned for a reality show,
"她來面試真人秀
so she just must be a gold-digging whore," Right?
那她肯定是個拜金的婊子"  對嗎
Isn't that the company line?
這不是你們公司的信條嗎
You hurt Becca
你傷害了貝卡
and no one believed her story,
沒有人相信她的說法
because you were perfect, Peter,
因為你那么完美  彼得
and you called her a liar, so that's what she was.
你說她是騙子  于是她就變成了騙子
And over time, it just ate her alive.
后來  她就慢慢被吞噬了
And I defended you
我維護你
because you're my brother,
是因為你是我的哥哥
not because I believed you, because I didn't.
不是因為我相信你  我不信
And that's just my cross to bear.
這就是我要背負的罪孽
Yeah, okay, you're...
好吧  你...
you're right.
你說得對
I'm sorry.
對不起
You have to drive right now. You have to drive right now!
你得趕緊開車  趕緊開車走
They're fuckin' witches!
她們是該死的女巫
- Did they tell you they're fuckin' witches?   -No, Peter! Stop it!
-她們沒告訴你她們是女巫嗎  -彼得  別說了
Listen to yourself!
聽聽你自己說的話
What the fuck? Okay.
搞什么  好吧
They did not say anything about that.
她們沒和我說過這個
- I'm gonna call Kara, and-- - No-- no, don't!
-我要打給卡拉  -不  不要
That's Kara!
那就是卡拉
No! No!
不  不
Peter, help me! Peter! Peter!
彼得  救我  彼得  彼得
Gwen! Gwen!
格溫  格溫
Oh, my... my hands...
我...我的手
No! No!
不  不
Ah! No!
不
Gwen, are you here?
格溫  你在嗎
Good morning, dear.
早上好  親愛的
- Where's my sister? - That's sweet.
-我妹妹呢  -你真好
Gwen woke up in her own bed.
格溫在自己的床上醒來
She'll have no memory of what happened here, so
她不會記得在這里發生的事  所以
unless you want her or anyone else, for that matter,
除非你想讓她或者其他人
to think you belong in an asylum,
認為你應該被送進精神病院
I suggest you take our little adventure
我建議你把我們之間的小小冒險
with you to the grave.
帶入墳墓  永不再提
What did you do to me?
你對我做了什么
For Becca.
為了貝卡
You fuck up once,
如果你再干壞事
you even think of hurting anyone ever again,
你再想要傷害任何人
we will bury you.
我們就埋了你
You'll never see it coming.
你根本預料不到
Are we clear?
明白了嗎
Yes, ma'am.
好的  女士
Thank you.
謝謝
We'll be watching, Peter.
我們會盯著你  彼得
Well, that was easy.
真簡單
Stockholm syndrome, anyone?
他斯德哥爾摩綜合征了嗎
He said thank you.
他說謝謝
- That was clutch. - Stakes.
-真老套  -釘子
Charges?
電擊器
Definitely day drinking, right?
絕對在白天就得喝一杯了
Jesus!
上帝啊
A hell of a party trick.
不錯的派對小把戲
Yeah, it's pretty good.
的確很不錯
Keep your phone on.
保持手機開機
He'll call you.
他會給你打電話
Not right away, but...
不是馬上  但是
- he'll call. - Right.
-他會打來的  -好的
You nailed that, by the way.
順便  你做得很好
Oh my God.
天啊
I was so nervous that he was gonna
我真的超級擔心他會
jump out of the car or push me out of the car
突然跳出車外  或者把我推出車外
before we got to the spot.
讓我們沒法演下去
Then I just... I lost my shit.
然后我...我就失控了
I mean, I really lost it.
我  我真的失控了
You were the perfect closer.
你是完美的壓軸
I'm so sorry, Kara.
我真的很抱歉  卡拉
I think about her every single day.
我每天都在想她
Yeah, me too.
我也是
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
天啊  真的很對不起
I'm so sorry.
對不起
These sheets smell like piss.
這些床單一股尿味
Final verdict on the micro dosing, ladies?
對我們用的劑量的最終決定呢  女士們
Well, the Datura was definitely the right species.
絕對得用曼陀羅
It's a nasty little fucker.
真是調皮的小東西
But we coulda used more.
但是我們能再多加點
That's on me. Yeah, I'm just growing into my alchemy.
都怪我  我的煉金術還需要練習
It's a delicate balance, 'cause you want him to go limp
這個平衡很微妙  因為我們希望他瘸
and see shit but not die, right?
出現幻覺  但不能死
Well, I just wanna say
我只是想說
thank you, obviously.
謝謝是肯定的
When Kara first called me, I admit I was skeptical.
卡拉剛給我打電話時  我承認我有所懷疑
But it sounds like you really reached him.
但是聽起來你們真的改變了他
Or he's just scared and thinks we put voodoo on his dick.
或者他只是怕了  以為我們給他的屌下了巫毒術
Maybe.
也許吧
But maybe not.
但也許不是
Well, it makes a difference to me.
對我來說有區別
He's my whole family.
他是我全部的家人了
You don't know him like I do.
你們不像我這么了解他
Well, we all have reasons for being here, right?
我們齊集一堂都有各自的理由  對嗎
My wedding is in three hours, Peter.
我的婚禮還有三小時就開始了  彼得
How can you possibly justify coming here?
你怎么有臉來
For one minute.
就一分鐘
I need to see our daughter, please.
我想見見我們的女兒  拜托你
One minute,
一分鐘
and that's it.
就行了
- Okay. - Jesus, you look like shit.
-就行了  -天啊  你看上去一團糟
Dad, what are you doing?
爸爸  你干什么
- You okay? - Yeah, um...
-你沒事吧  -沒事...
could we go for a walk?
我們能去散散步嗎
- Yeah. - Thank you.
-嗯  -謝謝你
To draining the swamp,
敬放干了沼澤
one bad hombre at a time.
一次一個壞男人
I think we can all drink to that.
我覺得我們都可以好好干一杯
Little stingy on the bubbly,
這些小泡泡
I'm gonna need three of these.
我能連喝三杯
Amazing!
太棒了
I've taken for granted how precious you are and...
我一直將你的可貴之處當做理所當然的饋贈
and you let me get away with it every time,
你每次也都原諒了我
but I don't want you to do that anymore.
但我不希望你再那樣做了
Not for me, not for any man.
不能為我  也不能為任何人這樣
No more lies, baby, okay?
我們再也不說謊了  寶貝
And I'm never gonna miss a thing.
我不會再錯過任何事
And I'll be at every soccer game from here on out,
我會參加你的每一場足球比賽
and I'm gonna be carrying one of those big plastic bags
我會跟其他父母一樣背著
of orange slices like those other parents do, okay?
裝滿橘子片的塑料袋  好嗎
Oh my God, Dad.
天啊  爸爸
Are you dying?
你要死了嗎
No, no, no, baby.
不不不  寶貝
I think maybe I should have.
我覺得我也許該死
But I'm still here,
但我還在這里
which makes me the luckiest man
所以我是全世界
on the planet.
最幸運的人
Riley, I love you...
萊利  我愛你
so much.
好愛你
I will see you tomorrow.
明天見
Not next weekend, tomorrow, okay?
不是下個周末  就明天  好嗎
What is this?
怎么回事
What, are you dying or something?
你要死了還是怎么著嗎
Laura, I'm so sorry I failed you
勞拉  我很抱歉  我在各個方面
on every conceivable level.
都辜負了你
It wasn't just me.
不僅僅是我
Hey, Peter.
彼得
Hi-- hi, hello.
你好
Uh... do we know each other?
我們認識嗎
We do now.
現在認識了
Be good.
乖乖的哦